A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2005-2010
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Virginia Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2005-2010
The Library of Virginia
44685
40.5 cu. ft (92 boxes)
Virginia. Office of the Secretary of Health and Human Resources
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and confidential information is restricted from public access for 75 years (Code of Virginia 42.1-78). Restricted records in this collection have been flagged but not removed. Types of flagged information may include, but is not limited to: medical records, financial records, vital statistics records, personal information including Social Security numbers, Social Services records, juvenile court records, administrative investigation records, attorney-client privileged documents, personnel records, proprietary information, and terrorism information and response records. Some documents may be closed in their entirety, while others may allow for redaction.
Acquisition Information
Accession 44685 transferred by Patricia Green, Office of the Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1111 E. Broad Street, Richmond, Virginia, 13 January 2010.
Biographical/Historical Information
In 1970, the Governor's Management Commission Study recommended the creation of six "Deputy Governors" to assist the Chief Executive in his managerial duties. Compatible functions of government were grouped under these administrative heads, who would serve as the Governor's top management team or "secretariats" as they are called now. Currently there are 8 secretariats in state government, which are: the Secretary of Administration; Secretary of Commerce and Trade; Secretary of Education; Secretary of Finance; Secretary of Health and Human Resources; Secretary of Natural Resources; Secretary of Public Safety; Secretary of Transportation.
The secretariat responsible for human services, health and welfare has gone through several reorganizations. In 1972, the General Assembly passed an act establishing the Secretary of Human Affairs. This office was responsible for management and direction of health and human services provided by the state for the citizens of the commonwealth. In 1976, the secretariat's name changed to the Secretary of Human Resources. With reorganization of state government, the secretariat name changed again to the Secretary of Health and Human Resources in 1988. The Secretary of Health and Human Resources oversees state agencies which provide services to Virginians with mental retardation, mental illness, substance abuse and physical disability concerns, and provide assistance to low-income families and to the aging community. Additionally, the agencies also license health practitioners and ensure safe drinking water in the Commonwealth.
During the administration of Governor Timothy Kaine, the Secretary of Health and Human Resources oversaw the following state agencies and boards: Dept. for the Aging; Dept. of Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, (previously Dept. of Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse Services); Dept. for the Blind and Vision Impaired; Dept. for the Deaf and Hard of Hearing; Dept. of Health, Dept. of Health Professions; Dept. of Medical Assistance Services; Dept. of Rehabilitation Services; Dept. of Social Services; Board for People with Disabilities; Tobacco Settlement Foundation; Office of the Comprehensive Services Act; and Virginia Foundation for Healthy Youth.
Marilyn B. Tavenner was appointed Secretary of Health and Human Resources in January 2006 by Governor Timothy M. Kaine. Secretary Tavenner spent 25 years working for Hospital Corporation of America (HCA) first as a nurse and later as CEO for Johnston-Willis and Chippenham hospitals in Richmond, Virginia and group President of Outpatient Services. After the end of the Kaine administration, Tavenner went on to serve as Principal Deputy Administrator of the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services and later as Acting Administrator.
Scope and Content
Contains records created and maintained by Secretary of Health and Human Resources, Marilyn B. Tavenner, during the administration of Governor Timothy M. Kaine. The records include incoming and outgoing correspondence with assigned agencies and constituents, subject files, decision memoranda, legislative files, budget material, and records related to activities and special projects.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Assigned State Agencies, 2005-2009
Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Constituents, 2005-2009
Series III. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, 2005-2010
Series IV. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary - Constituent Letters, 2006-2009
Series V. Decision Memoranda and Briefs, 2006-2009
Series VI. Legislative Files, 2006-2009
Series VII. Planning and Budget Files - Assigned State Agencies, 2006-2007
Series VIII. Public Relations, Activities and Visits, 2006-2007
Series IX. Special Projects and Studies, 2006-2009
Contents List
- Series I. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Assigned State Agencies, 2005-2009., Extent: 4.95 cu. ft. (11 boxes).
  Contains correspondence and subject files created and maintained by the Office of the Secretary of Health and Human Resources that pertain to the agencies and boards under its purview and other health-related entities. Included are incoming and outgoing correspondence with agency heads and other officials, memoranda, reports of the Department of Behavioral Health and Developmental Services made by the Inspector General, files on assisted living facility regulations, Medicaid, septic system grants, and the Senior Navigator program.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of agency and then alphabetically by topic.
  - Aging, Dept. for the, 2006-2007. (Box 001, Folder 1)
  - Aging, Dept. for the - National Governor's Association, 2008. (Box 001, Folder 2)
  - Aging, Dept. for the - NatLUST/Home Septic Systems, 2008. (Box 001, Folder 3)
  - Aging, Dept. for the - Project 2012 Grant Proposal, 2006. (Box 001, Folder 4)
  - Aging, Dept. for the - Senior Community Service Employment Program (SCSEP), 2008. (Box 001, Folder 5)
  - Aging, Dept. for the - Senior Navigator, 2005-2007. (Box 001, Folder 6)
  - Aging, Dept. for the - Senior Navigator, 2005-2007. (Box 001, Folder 7)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of, 2006-2009. (Box 001, Folder 8)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Auxiliary Grant Portability Feasibility Study, 2008. (Box 001, Folder 9)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Budget, 2006. (Box 001, Folder 10)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Central Virginia Training Center Visit, 2006. (Box 001, Folder 11)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Children's Mental Health, 2006; undated. (Box 001, Folder 12)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Civil Admissions/Commitment, 2005-2006. (Box 002, Folder 1)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Community Service Board Agreements, 2006. (Box 002, Folder 2)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Comprehensive State Plan (2006-2012), 2005. (Box 002, Folder 3)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Comprehensive State Plan (2008-2014), 2007. (Box 002, Folder 4)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Employee Investigations, 2009. (Box 002, Folder 5)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Financial Report, 2005. (Box 002, Folder 6)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Governor's System Transformation Initiative, 2006. (Box 002, Folder 7)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Hiram W. Davis Medical Center, undated. (Box 002, Folder 8)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Individuals with Disabilities Education Act (IDEA) Assurances, 2006-2009. (Box 002, Folder 9)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Initiatives (FY 2008), 2007. (Box 002, Folder 10)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Investigation of Critical Incident at Virginia Tech (Office of the Inspector General), 2007. (Box 002, Folder 11)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Involuntary Commitment, 2007. (Box 002, Folder 12)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Juvenile Competency to Stand Trial, 2006. (Box 002, Folder 13)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Memoranda, 2006. (Box 002, Folder 14)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Memoranda, 2007. (Box 002, Folder 15)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Memoranda, 2008. (Box 003, Folder 1)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Reports, 2006-2007. (Box 003, Folder 2)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Reports (Office of the Inspector General), 2005. (Box 003, Folder 3)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Reports (Office of the Inspector General), 2005. (Box 003, Folder 4)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Reports (Office of the Inspector General), 2006. (Box 003, Folder 5)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Reports (Office of the Inspector General), 2006-2007. (Box 003, Folder 6)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Reports (Office of the Inspector General), 2007-2009. (Box 003, Folder 7)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Sexually Violent Predators, 2006. (Box 003, Folder 8)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Southwestern Virginia Mental Health Institute, 2006. (Box 003, Folder 9)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Southwestern Virginia Training Center, undated. (Box 004, Folder 1)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Virginia Center for Behavioral Rehabilitation, 2006. (Box 004, Folder 2)
  - Behavioral Health and Developmental Services, Dept. of - Western State Hospital, 2006-2009. (Box 004, Folder 3)
  - Blind and Vision Impaired, Dept. for the, 2006-2008. (Box 004, Folder 4)
  - Deaf and Hard of Hearing, Dept. for the, 2007. (Box 004, Folder 5)
  - Deaf and Hard of Hearing, Dept. for the - VaRelay, 2008. (Box 004, Folder 6)
  - Health, Dept. of, 2006. (Box 004, Folder 7)
  - Health, Dept. of, 2007-2008. (Box 004, Folder 8)
  - Health, Dept. of - Abstinence, 2007. (Box 004, Folder 9)
  - Health, Dept. of - Abstinence, 2007. (Box 004, Folder 10)
  - Health, Dept. of - Audit, State Employee Fraud, Waste and Abuse Hotline Case, 2006. (Box 004, Folder 11)
  - Health, Dept. of - Disclosure Assistance Services, 2007. (Box 004, Folder 12)
  - Health, Dept. of - Drinking Water, 2007-2009. (Box 004, Folder 13)
  - Health, Dept. of - Emergency Preparedness, 2006-2007. (Box 004, Folder 14)
  - Health, Dept. of - EMS Maintenance Mandate, 2008. (Box 004, Folder 15)
  - Health, Dept. of - FOIA Request, Delegate Marshall (Abortion), 2006. (Box 004, Folder 16)
  - Health, Dept. of - Health Commissioner, 2007-2008. (Box 005, Folder 1)
  - Health, Dept. of - Healthy States Grant, 2006. (Box 005, Folder 2)
  - Health, Dept. of - Hepatitis Vaccines, 2007. (Box 005, Folder 3)
  - Health, Dept. of - HPV Vaccine, 2006. (Box 005, Folder 4)
  - Health, Dept. of - NatLUST (Septic System Financing), 2006-2007. (Box 005, Folder 5)
  - Health, Dept. of - Office of Health Policy and Planning Program Summary, 2006. (Box 005, Folder 6)
  - Health, Dept. of - Richmond City Dept. of Public Health, 2006. (Box 005, Folder 7)
  - Health, Dept. of - Suffolk Dept. of Health and Dept. of Social Services Co-location, 2006. (Box 005, Folder 8)
  - Health, Dept. of - "The Impact of HIV/AIDS Among Black Women in Virginia," 2006. (Box 005, Folder 9)
  - Health, Dept. of - WIC Grant, 2007. (Box 005, Folder 10)
  - Health Professions, Dept. of, 2005-2006. (Box 005, Folder 11)
  - Health Professions, Dept. of, 2007-2009. (Box 005, Folder 12)
  - Health Professions, Dept. of - Biennial Reports, 2006; 2008. (Box 005, Folder 13)
  - Health Professions, Dept. of - Pain Management Regulations, 2007-2009. (Box 005, Folder 14)
  - Health Professions, Dept. of - Pain Management Regulations, 2007-2009. (Box 006, Folder 1)
  - Health Professions, Dept. of - Relocation, 2006. (Box 006, Folder 2)
  - Health Professions, Dept. of - Security Breach, 2009. (Box 006, Folder 3)
  - Long-term Care Administrators, Board of, undated. (Box 006, Folder 4)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 2005-2006. (Box 006, Folder 5)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 2006-2008. (Box 006, Folder 6)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of - Asset Transfer, 2007. (Box 006, Folder 7)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of - Auditor Reports, 2006. (Box 006, Folder 8)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of - Budget (2008), 2007. (Box 006, Folder 9)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of - Hearing (Nickerson), 2007-2008. (Box 006, Folder 10)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of - Hearing (Nickerson), 2007-2008. (Box 006, Folder 11)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of - Reports, 2006-2008. (Box 007, Folder 1)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of - Robert Wood Johnson Foundation Grant, 2006. (Box 007, Folder 2)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of - Statistical Record of the Virginia Medicaid Program, 2005. (Box 007, Folder 3)
  - Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of - Statistical Record of the Virginia Medicaid Program, 2006. (Box 007, Folder 4)
  - People with Disabilities, Board for, 2006-2009. (Box 007, Folder 5)
  - Protection and Advocacy, Virginia Office for, 2006. (Box 007, Folder 6)
  - Rehabilitation Council, Virginia State, 2007. (Box 007, Folder 7)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of, 2006-2008. (Box 007, Folder 8)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Disability Reviews/Hearings, undated. (Box 007, Folder 9)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Hearing (Elouadghiri), 2008-2009. (Box 007, Folder 10)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Hearing (Elouadghiri), 2008-2009. (Box 008, Folder 1)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Hearing (Elouadghiri), 2008-2009. (Box 008, Folder 2)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Hearing (Elouadghiri), 2008-2009. (Box 008, Folder 3)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Hearing (Elouadghiri), 2008-2009. (Box 008, Folder 4)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Hearing (Elouadghiri), 2008-2009. (Box 008, Folder 5)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Review (Hall), 2007. (Box 008, Folder 6)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Review (Haranzo), 2007. (Box 008, Folder 7)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Review (Lynch), 2006-2007. (Box 009, Folder 1)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Review (Silverthorn), 2006. (Box 009, Folder 2)
  - Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of - Statewide Independent Living Council, 2007. (Box 009, Folder 3)
  - Social Services, Dept. of, 2006-2009. (Box 009, Folder 4)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Administration for Children and Families, 2006. (Box 009, Folder 5)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Adoption Subsidies for Children with Special Needs, 2006. (Box 009, Folder 6)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Assisted Living Facility Regulations, 2006. (Box 009, Folder 7)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Assisted Living Facility Regulations, 2006. (Box 009, Folder 8)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Assisted Living Facility Regulations, 2006. (Box 009, Folder 9)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Cherrix Case, 2006. (Box 009, Folder 10)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Child Advocacy Center Funding, 2007. (Box 010, Folder 1)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Congressional Briefing, 2007. (Box 010, Folder 2)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Council on the Status of Women, 2007-2008. (Box 010, Folder 3)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Covenant Daughters Ministry, 2006. (Box 010, Folder 4)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Division of Family Services Organizational Survey and Report, 2006. (Box 010, Folder 5)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - GAO Report on the Child Support Enforcement Program, 2006. (Box 010, Folder 6)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Legal Cases/Issues, 2007-2009. (Box 010, Folder 7)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Low Income Home Energy Assistance Program, 2006. (Box 010, Folder 8)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Memoranda, 2006-2009. (Box 010, Folder 9)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Suffolk Health Dept., 2006. (Box 010, Folder 10)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - SupportKids Litigation Proposal, 2007. (Box 010, Folder 11)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Temporary Assistance for Needy Families (TANF), 2006-2009. (Box 010, Folder 12)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Virginia Independence Program Reports, 2006. (Box 011, Folder 1)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Virginia Independence Program Reports, 2006. (Box 011, Folder 2)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Virginia Independence Program Reports, 2007. (Box 011, Folder 3)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - Virginia Poverty Law Center, 2006. (Box 011, Folder 4)
  - Social Services, Dept. of - VISSTA, 2007. (Box 011, Folder 5)
  - State Emergency Medical Services Advisory Board - Apppointments, 2006. (Box 011, Folder 6)
- Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Constituents, 2005-2009., Extent: 11.7 cu. ft. (26 boxes).
  Contains incoming correspondence from constituents and other non-governmental entities sent directly to the Secretary of Health and Human Resources or referred to the Secretary from the Office of the Governor for response. Also included is the outgoing correspondence from the Secretary as well as supporting documentation and correspondence from related agency officials. Topics of interest include the Abraham Cherrix case (Virginia v. Cherrix), the use of biosolids in farming, assisted living facility regulations, the HPV vaccine, universal medical coverage, and the potential closure of Virginia's training centers. A large percentage of the letters pertain to child support enforcement, the use of Temporary Assistance for Needy Families (TANF), vital statistics records issues, mental health waivers, and Medicare concerns.
  Arranged numerically by database number which is generally chronological by date of response letter.
  - 2560044 - 2564056, 2005. (Box 012, Folder 1)
  - 2567621 - 2568776, 2006 January. (Box 012, Folder 2)
  - 2568780 - 2571723, 2006 January-February. (Box 012, Folder 3)
  - 2571834 - 2573671, 2006 February. (Box 012, Folder 4)
  - 2573728 - 2576172, 2006 February-March. (Box 012, Folder 5)
  - 2576222 - 2580385, 2006 March. (Box 012, Folder 6)
  - 2580453 - 2584233, 2006 March-April. (Box 012, Folder 7)
  - 2584272 - 2587963, 2006 April. (Box 012, Folder 8)
  - 2588066 - 2591144, 2006 April. (Box 013, Folder 1)
  - 2591304 - 2593250, 2006 April-May. (Box 013, Folder 2)
  - 2593417 - 2594829, 2006 May. (Box 013, Folder 3)
  - 2594932 - 2595593, 2006 May. (Box 013, Folder 4)
  - 2595594 - 2596471, 2006 May. (Box 013, Folder 5)
  - 2596538 - 2597626, 2006 May-June. (Box 013, Folder 6)
  - 2597637 - 2598718, 2006 June. (Box 013, Folder 7)
  - 2598901 - 2600087, 2006 June. (Box 014, Folder 1)
  - 2600109 - 2603176, 2006 June. (Box 014, Folder 2)
  - 2603187 - 2604668, 2006 June-July. (Box 014, Folder 3)
  - 2604678 - 2605692, 2006 July. (Box 014, Folder 4)
  - 2605676 - 2608667, 2006 July. (Box 014, Folder 5)
  - 2608725 - 2609452, 2006 August. (Box 014, Folder 6)
  - 2609465 - 2610221, 2006 August. (Box 015, Folder 1)
  - 2610279 - 2610884, 2006 August. (Box 015, Folder 2)
  - 2611004 - 2612610, 2006 August. (Box 015, Folder 3)
  - 2612613 - 2613764, 2006 August-September. (Box 015, Folder 4)
  - 2613766 - 2615104, 2006 September. (Box 015, Folder 5)
  - 2615111 - 2617640, 2006 September. (Box 015, Folder 6)
  - 2617646 - 2618381, 2006 September. (Box 015, Folder 7)
  - 2618437 - 2619273, 2006 September. (Box 016, Folder 1)
  - 2619295 - 2619965, 2006 September-October. (Box 016, Folder 2)
  - 2620033 - 2620983, 2006 October. (Box 016, Folder 3)
  - 2620987 - 2621921, 2006 October. (Box 016, Folder 4)
  - 2621936 - 2623158, 2006 October-November. (Box 016, Folder 5)
  - 2623160 - 2624199, 2006 October-November. (Box 016, Folder 6)
  - 2624206 - 2624765, 2006 November. (Box 016, Folder 7)
  - 2624780 - 2626103, 2006 November. (Box 017, Folder 1)
  - 2626103 - 2628639, 2006 November-December. (Box 017, Folder 2)
  - 2628871 - 2629781, 2006 December. (Box 017, Folder 3)
  - 2630020 - 2632163, 2006 December. (Box 017, Folder 4)
  - 2632173 - 2632638, 2006 December. (Box 017, Folder 5)
  - 2632652 - 2633332, 2007 January. (Box 017, Folder 6)
  - 2633343 - 2634223, 2007 January. (Box 017, Folder 7)
  - 2634229 - 2635026, 2007 January. (Box 017, Folder 8)
  - 2635064 - 2635667, 2007 January. (Box 018, Folder 1)
  - 2635678 - 2636965, 2007 January. (Box 018, Folder 2)
  - 2636966 - 2637475, 2007 January. (Box 018, Folder 3)
  - 2637512 - 2639951, 2007 January-February. (Box 018, Folder 4)
  - 2640071 - 2642246, 2007 February. (Box 018, Folder 5)
  - 2642275 - 2643717, 2007 February. (Box 018, Folder 6)
  - 2643718 - 2644795, 2007 February. (Box 018, Folder 7)
  - 2644910 - 2646505, 2007 February-March. (Box 019, Folder 1)
  - 2646559 - 2649319, 2007 March. (Box 019, Folder 2)
  - 2649629 - 2652372, 2007 March. (Box 019, Folder 3)
  - 2652489 - 2655795, 2007 March. (Box 019, Folder 4)
  - 2655802 - 2659977, 2007 March. (Box 019, Folder 5)
  - 2660005 - 2662674, 2007 April. (Box 019, Folder 6)
  - 2662725 - 2664227, 2007 April. (Box 020, Folder 1)
  - 2664229 - 2665528, 2007 April-May. (Box 020, Folder 2)
  - 2665530 - 2667786, 2007 May. (Box 020, Folder 3)
  - 2667790 - 2668966, 2007 May. (Box 020, Folder 4)
  - 2668968 - 2669990, 2007 May. (Box 020, Folder 5)
  - 2670000 - 2671131, 2007 May-June. (Box 020, Folder 6)
  - 2671220 - 2672290, 2007 June. (Box 020, Folder 7)
  - 2672297 - 2674237, 2007 June. (Box 021, Folder 1)
  - 2674324 - 2675279, 2007 June. (Box 021, Folder 2)
  - 2675322 - 2676101, 2007 June. (Box 021, Folder 3)
  - 2676103 - 2676851, 2007 June. (Box 021, Folder 4)
  - 2676867 - 2677654, 2007 June. (Box 021, Folder 5)
  - 2677657 - 2679580, 2007 June-July. (Box 021, Folder 6)
  - 2679621 - 2680770, 2007 July. (Box 022, Folder 1)
  - 2680781 - 2682436, 2007 July. (Box 022, Folder 2)
  - 2682443 - 2678788, 2007 July. (Box 022, Folder 3)
  - 2678819 - 2683719, 2007 July-August. (Box 022, Folder 4)
  - 2683744 - 2685090, 2007 August. (Box 022, Folder 5)
  - 2685095 - 2686032, 2007 August. (Box 022, Folder 6)
  - 2686034 - 2687336, 2007 August. (Box 023, Folder 1)
  - 2687366 - 2688389, 2007 August. (Box 023, Folder 2)
  - 2688390 - 2689485, 2007 August-September. (Box 023, Folder 3)
  - 2689491 - 2689854, 2007 September. (Box 023, Folder 4)
  - 2689895 - 2691524, 2007 September. (Box 023, Folder 5)
  - 2691597 - 2692877, 2007 September. (Box 023, Folder 6)
  - 2692879 - 2693666, 2007 September. (Box 023, Folder 7)
  - 2693701 - 2694091, 2007 September-October. (Box 024, Folder 1)
  - 2694110 - 2694894, 2007 October. (Box 024, Folder 2)
  - 2694925 - 2695890, 2007 October. (Box 024, Folder 3)
  - 2695923 - 2697182, 2007 October. (Box 024, Folder 4)
  - 2697183 - 2699248, 2007 October. (Box 024, Folder 5)
  - 2699329 - 2699950, 2007 October-November. (Box 024, Folder 6)
  - 2700016 - 2700558, 2007 October-November. (Box 025, Folder 1)
  - 2700560 - 2701319, 2007 November. (Box 025, Folder 2)
  - 2701361 - 2702507, 2007 November. (Box 025, Folder 3)
  - 2702513 - 2707851, 2007 November-December. (Box 025, Folder 4)